What kind of daughter are you?
Before you ask me
what kind of daughter I am,
why don't you ask her
what kind of mother she is?
Why'd you come here?
Nanny Cora, can we stay here?
We now have a solution to our problems.
-Enough!
-That's enough!
That's enough!
I just thought you've changed.
But I thought wrong.
You don't need another
fake smiling campaign.
What you need…
is a tell-all sit-down interview.
The mother and daughter
will face each other.
This Sunday on…
Uncovered.
Diana, Patricia, welcome to Uncovered.
Welcome to the program.
And thank you very much.
First, let's talk about…
the video.
What is this about?
Oh, uh…
It was just a big misunderstanding.
As you all know,
I was still recovering from an illness.
And…
I was quite disoriented
when I saw them at my house.
But we've talked it all out.
I've made amends already.
How did you…
make amends?
Okay, we'll talk about that later,
but before that,
how does it feel that
you guys are reunited now?
Well, we haven't been together
for a long time,
so we're still adjusting.
What matters is that my mother is safe.
La Familia.
But now that I'm talking to you…
where is this family as we're speaking?
As you know, my father was the one
who started La Familia,
and I continued to run it.
And, uh…
for me, it's not just a company.
Uh…
It's about family.
We may have some disagreements,
but it's about the people
you care the most about.
It's about the bonds that
survive time and distance.
Thank you.
Patricia, you seem like
a devoted daughter.
Um…
Did you find it hard
to forgive each other?
Well, you know,
forgiveness is not like a switch, right?
You can't just turn it on or off.
It's a decision, and…
I choose my daughter.
And I chose to understand her as well.
If she didn't have a heart attack…
what do you think would be
your situation right now?
We'd still be fighting.
Just kidding.
And still…
And still missing each other.
Well, um…
Diana, you won't be missing
Patricia anymore
because I have it from good sources,
that Patricia will be
working at La Familia.
Yes!
Are you excited?
Very excited.
It looks like…
your daughter, Patricia,
will continue La Familia's legacy.
How do you feel about it?
That's what I've always wanted.
It's official.
Here at Uncovered,
we are officially welcoming
Patricia to La Familia.
Patricia, welcome back home.
Okay, cut!
What was that?
Working at La Familia
wasn't part of the deal.
I thought we'd only do
a photoshoot and an interview.
I'm just sticking with the narrative.
Diana also said how important
legacy is to La Familia.
Lip service is not enough.
Words without actions are meaningless.
The people won't believe you.
I have a job, okay?
What job?
Your job is unstable.
Patricia, you should play the part.
Think of it as your biggest break.
You will be paid as well.
Don't you see it?
There's a reason why
I stayed away from my mother.
I'm not going to force you.
Do you have any other jobs
or opportunities to choose from?
The million you will earn here
is just enough to pay off
your father's debts.
Will you earn that
while working as a talent?
Fine, let's just say that you
continue working as a talent.
But we all know that
it is not a stable job.
You won't always book a job.
So, just think of…
what you will do in La Familia
as your training,
as your fallback for your family.
I am guiding both of you…
towards a situation
that will benefit both of you.
It's not just Diana
who'll benefit from this.
It will also change your life.
What you're saying is additional work.
That should incur additional payment…
separate from the prior million.
I think that's workable.
Was that part of your deal?
You don't have to do that.
They said it's necessary.
They will pay me.
No.
Just give them back the money.
The money that we need?
Pa…
Sir Ricardo is right.
The money I make as a talent
is no longer enough.
They will pay me a lot of money.
It will be help us a lot.
We'll have money
for rent, electricity, water,
April and Jena's tuition,
for your medicines,
and all our other expenses here at home.
Patricia…
Are you sure?
Because, I'll warn you, I know Diana well.
She is very wicked. Can you handle it?
We still have to see each other anyway.
Why?
To receive her payment.
She said she'd pay me in installments.
See?
You know, Diana is just
on another level, isn't she?
But, you know, you'll manage because…
I raised you.
We need to control the narrative.
I want the interview
and the campaign everywhere.
-Bro.
-Hm?
-Chairmom is your employer, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Doesn't she look like
she really loves her daughter?
What parent doesn't love their child?
You have a point.
Pay top influencers…
lifestyle vloggers,
and mommy creators for reactions.
But the paid partnerships
should look organic.
Hey, look.
Patricia is just like my daughter.
-She has a point, doesn't she?
-Yes.
Boost positive engagement
and drown out the negative noise.
They argue just like us, don't they?
I think I'm craving Cala Soda.
-Should we buy some?
-Sure.
All right.
Anything defamatory or malicious,
flag it immediately.
We won't allow hate to be trending.
Patricia, I'll use your outfit, okay?
-You can have it.
-Okay!
Wait a minute.
Let's take a selfie, bestie.
I'll make a vlog.
I have a famous friend now!
Why are you taking photos
with just you two?
Include us!
Right! Go there.
We are officially welcoming Patricia…
to La Familia.
Patricia, welcome back home.
Since the launch of the campaign…
we've received a lot of positive comments.
The negative comments
are greatly outnumbered.
Cala Soda is back at number one.
So…
Congratulations.
I kept my promise.
But I have to admit,
this wouldn't have happened
if you and Patricia hadn't agreed to it.
Your idea to take her into…
La Familia…
was a master stroke.
That's why you're the Chairmom.
Stop it with the empty flattery.
Patricia shouldn't know
what we talked about.
About her working at La Familia?
Why did you decide to do that?
Have you seen Patricia's life?
She's still an Aragon.
I won't let her life go astray.
I have to keep an eye on her.
Just like a mother.
Your one percent company share.
You are La Familia's
new head of public relations.
I've already signed the contract.
Just return that to me
once you're done with it.
But the issue about
the poisoning isn't over yet.
We can't be distracted.
It all started there.
There are still people
who don't accept the settlement.
I want this to finally end.
I looked into what happened.
There were markers
for an organized demolition.
We checked the other accounts.
This was all done within
the last week of the attack.
The timing, the messages…
someone controlled it.
Are you saying that
the poisoning was planned?
The question is…
who has a grudge against you?
I think the better question is…
who doesn't hold a grudge against me?
Go ahead with the plan.
That's the first installment
for our payment.
Oh, finally.
-Thank you.
-My goodness!
Are you really going
to pay us in installments?
We saw you on TV!
You were even bragging to us
that you were the child of a CEO!
Right?
Just be grateful that you're getting paid
even if it's in installments.
Wait a minute, when is your next payment?
-Next month.
-Okay, fine.
Just make sure to pay us!
You might hide from us again.
-Right!
-He's right!
That will never happen.
-Okay, fine. Let's get going.
-Thank you.
-Pay us again next time.
-We'll be back.
They finally paid.
Have you decided yet, dear?
Yes.
I will work at La Familia.
We need the money.
They told me that I could also keep doing
what I'm already doing.
Just make sure that they will
hold their end of the deal.
It might be a good thing, too.
How so?
Well, if Patricia would inherit
all of it anyway,
then it would be better
if she would start training
on how to run their business, right?
Hey, cuz!
So, the rumors are true.
You're going to work here.
That's a good look on you.
Very vintage.
Very abstract.
Very…
grandmother's attic.
It suits you.
Hey, Georgia, we have to go.
-Excuse me.
-We'll get going then.
Bye!
I love my life. I love my life.
I love my life.
-Good morning, Ms. D.
-Ms. D?
That's what your employees
call you, right?
I'm now an employee of La Familia too.
I don't want people to think that
you're giving me any special treatment.
I know where my station is.
-Enzo.
-Yes, Ms. D?
Brief Patricia on what her job entails,
and especially the dress code.
-Copy, Ms. D.
-We're right on time!
Ms. D and Patricia are already here.
Ah, sorry. Excuse me.
Patricia!
Welcome to La Familia.
The only daughter's
first day at La Familia.
Picture, picture! Take your photos.
Let's go, let's go.
Smile, smile.
Keep taking photos, guys.
You there!
Hurry up!
-What's going on?
-Diana Aragon! Come out!
-Come and face us!
-What?
-What's happening? What's going on?
-Give us justice!
I'll call security, Ms. D.
Security!
Patricia!
Where are you going?
I'm going to talk with them.
Are you out of your mind?
Diana, let's go inside.
There's a lot of press here.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go inside!
Didn't I assign this to you?
But you prioritized the press earlier
to make a spectacle
out of me and my daughter.
I had a schedule to talk to them today.
Maybe they've heard that
we had the press here,
so they rushed to make some noise.
Why didn't you just let me talk to them?
Whatever you say could become a liability.
That's why I don't just let
anybody talk with them.
You need training for that.
Besides, it's not part
of your job description.
Then what am I really supposed to do here?
Just follow Enzo's lead.
And please,
can we do our jobs right this time?
Let me help you.
No thanks, I can handle it.
-Just give it to me.
-But…
I was just being kind earlier,
but I got reprimanded.
This is the company's uniform room.
We have a standard here
for business formal
because Ms. D doesn't want
her employees to look sloppy.
Number one,
neutral colors only.
No loud colors, please.
It should also be well-fit.
It's to avoid distractions
because we all need
to only focus on our work.
It's also your way of showing respect.
Your respect for others.
Your respect for the company you work for.
And the respect you want
others to give you.
So that's why you all look the same here.
I'll give the employee manual
to you later.
Read and understand it carefully.
It's important.
Wait a second.
I just want to clarify our deal.
I won't come in here
every day on a regular basis.
I'm not going to stay here permanently.
I have a life of my own.
But when you agreed to the deal,
you also agreed to follow the rules.
This suits me.
Too big.
Why?
I just remembered how when I was a kid,
things were exactly like this!
There were a lot of rules,
a lot of orders.
She even decided
what clothes I had to wear!
She wasn't looking for a child.
She wanted a doll.
A doll that she could dress up
and that would do everything she wanted.
It was your decision
to work here, wasn't it?
Hm.
Then see it to the end.
Uh…
I can't afford these.
It's fine.
That's one of the benefits
of working here.
Here, wear this.
-Huh?
-Give me your feet.
I know how to wear shoes.
We have so much to do here in the office.
You were even late earlier.
It was just five minutes!
The jeep I was riding in stopped working.
Let me do it.
Do you have any idea how hard it is
to take public transport?
You don't know it because you have a car.
-Your other foot.
-I wonder if your car…
stops working, do you still
not take public transportation?
How do you go to places, then?
Besides, it's impossible.
Have you never been late
in your entire life?
Ah… It's freezing!
-Give me your foot.
-Argh!
-The other one.
-Jesus Christ.
First lesson you'll learn in La Familia,
there are no excuses.
You can change in the restroom.
Are you okay?
Yes.
-Are you okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Here.
That manual contains
all the policies, tasks,
and your responsibilities
as an office assistant.
That's why you must memorize that.
But in general, you'll also do
all the errands in the office.
Okay? Let me show you to your desk.
Here's what you asked for, Sir Enzo.
Thanks, Sid.
This is my desk?
Looks great.
No.
This is your desk.
And this is your first task.
Have all the employees sign
the attendance sheet.
When I say everyone, I mean everyone.
From security, utility,
maintenance, etcetera.
From the first floor to the 20th floor.
Haven't you heard of biometrics?
Your building looks great,
but it isn't up to date.
Don't you have that here?
Ms. D asked for that.
You need to finish it within the day.
Once you're done,
you can report immediately
to the admin manager for your other tasks.
All right?
I'll leave you to it.
-Sir, wait.
-Hmm?
Since you're here, why don't
you sign the attendance sheet?
Okay.
Thank you.
Good luck.
AUGUST 3RD 1992
Fight, Patricia.
I love my life.
We will be completely
transparent with you.
One thing is for sure,
all your needs will be met.
Just like what we did
with the other victims.
I know that you'll silence us with money.
You can't just pay us off!
Just because we are poor
doesn't mean you can step on us.
Right! He's right!
You can't fool everyone
with your promises.
What we want…
is for your boss to pay!
Put Diana Aragon in jail!
Put her in jail!
A FAMILY IS COMPLETE WITH CALA SODA
Tenth floor.
Accounting and Finance.
Ah.
-Sir Joseph Vargas?
-Ah, yes?
Please sign the attendance sheet.
Ah, yes.
So you're the one going around
to get the attendance.
Ah, yes.
There are a lot of employees here.
I already went to three floors.
I have five left.
Ah! I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, but could you
please sign the attendance?
I'm sorry.
Ah… Marco Majes, right?
Could you sign as well?
Please wash your hands before you sign.
You're the new office assistant, right?
-Yes.
-Well…
this is needed on the eighth floor.
Could you please hand this over to them?
-If it's okay?
-Yes, of course!
How's the meeting earlier?
Hold on. Where are you heading?
Kidding. Before you leave
could you sign this for me?
Please sign this.
Thank you.
Hello? Yes.
We were talking to your staff earlier.
They want to settle.
I already convinced my companions
to refuse, just like you said.
How long will we refuse to settle?
Their offer for damages is quite large.
Hold on.
Aren't they your co-workers?
This might lead to an investigation,
I don't want to get in trouble.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Um… I'm just getting some air.
What about you?
Nothing.
Aren't you with
La Familia's lawyers earlier?
Your watch looks nice.
Looks expensive.
I got this for a low price.
And besides, it's fake.
And your phone,
that's the new model, right?
-I wanted to get that.
-Then do it.
What do I care?
I need the new draft
on administrative process by tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am.
Here's what you asked for.
When I said I wanted everyone's signature,
I expected everyone, including those
in the janitorial services department.
Excuse me, ma'am.
This is complete.
I actually found so much about them.
You still have a lot of things to do.
Just wait for further instructions.
Yes, ma'am.
Ms. D.
About the rally…
they're still out there.
They don't want to accept the offers.
Didn't I tell you
to offer something higher?
Make it double or even triple!
Noted, Ms. D.
Is there something funny?
I thought that maybe
that's not what they need.
When people are in need,
they are desperate for someone to talk to.
Do you think it's that easy?
You don't know what's at stake here.
What they've been through isn't a joke.
I was just thinking about the victims.
Me too.
That's why I'm making sure
that there is still a company standing
who'll take accountability
and will help them.
This is just your first day here,
you think you know everything.
You think you know better than us
who has worked for decades
who worked very hard
to keep this company afloat.
Please make room
so you won't get dispersed.
And so you won't disrupt their work.
Please move.
We need to talk to someone, sir.
You're bothering the workers.
-We're rallying.
-We need help, sir!
We just need someone to hear us out.
Bugoy! Son!
Bugoy, are you hurt?
I told you not to stray far from me.
-He… He's fine.
-Does it hurt?
He's fine, don't get mad at him.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Ah… what's your name?
Rosenda. My name is Rosenda.
My name is Patricia.
Can I talk to you in private?
I work for La Familia.
I am not the one you should be talking to.
You should talk to Carlo. He's our leader.
I want to talk to the mothers.
I want to know why
you won't settle with us.
We really didn't want
to blow the issue up anymore.
The lawyer of La Familia
already talked to us.
But…
Carlo didn't like it.
He said it wasn't enough.
He said that we should file a complaint.
He said that if we caused more trouble,
they'll offer something bigger.
That's right.
That's why we should talk to Carlo
because he's the one stopping us.
Is that so?
Carlo has a point.
What my son has been through isn't easy.
And besides, this isn't just about money.
When my son got poisoned,
I didn't know what to do.
You'll understand
once you become a mother.
Every mother is like this.
I hope you understand our situation.
Trust me.
I understand you all.
I understand you, Rosenda.
But…
it doesn't have to get this messy, right?
We are ready to listen to you.
La Familia is ready to listen to you.
Why don't you talk to Carlo about this?
Rosenda.
As you said earlier…
you are a mother.
You are the ones
who understand the situation best.
There are a lot of children affected.
So please, allow me to help you.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
Help me convince the mothers
who are with you.
There's a way for this to be settled.
What have you thought of?
Miss, where's Patricia's office?
The owner's daughter.
He's the father of the owner's daughter.
Right there, sir.
Give us a cup of coffee later.
Hurry with that, okay?
Ah, miss?
Is this Patricia's office?
This space doesn't seem quite right
for the owner's daughter's office.
Oh, no.
That's actually her table.
She's our new assistant.
If you'll excuse me.
This is her office?
This is where she put Patricia?
-Yes.
-Look.
Look at what she's done to our daughter.
Sir.
Based on the preliminary results,
it does not appear to be an accident.
It was intentional?
Here. Take a look, sir.
There is no trace of contamination
on the other soda batches.
But everyone who got sick,
came from the feeding
program distribution.
So it was done on a specific channel.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-It seems targeted.
What is this?
This is an internal investigation.
-Teddy.
-That's Mr. Aragon to you.
Is this part of your job?
In order to fix something broken,
I need to know how it broke.
I'm just doing my job.
Are there some things
that I shouldn't know?
What exactly
are you trying to say?
Ms. D, Patricia is talking
to the victims downstairs.
What?
Who told her to do that?
Ms. D!
I have something to tell you.
Why are you meddling in things
that have nothing to do
with your scope of work?
What?
You're unbelievable!
Why are you talking to the victims?
-Who told you to do that?
-Diana!
Why are you yelling at my daughter?
You have no right
to talk to her like that.
And what are you doing here?
Visiting her.
Thankfully, I did. Because if I didn't,
I wouldn't know that
you would treat her this way.
Of course, you're freaking out
without knowing anything.
I was reprimanding her
because she did something wrong.
She's not trained for that.
What if she got in danger?
What if she said something
to harm the company?
Do you even understand the legal risks?
Until now, is that what you think of me?
I talked to them because
they needed someone to talk to.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was helping.
Here's a list of those willing
to negotiate for a settlement.
Those who were opposed to it
are open and waiting now.
See?
You should be thankful, Diana.
No, that is not the point.
You do not make decisions
on your own, Patricia.
We have a protocol to follow.
What you've done out there
with no clearance,
that can put the whole company at risk.
Just say you're mad at Patricia!
We saw the desk you assigned her in.
-You put her in a small…
-Quit butting in.
Is that how little you think of Patricia?
I don't need to explain anything to you.
But for the sake of your peace of mind,
I assigned her as an office assistant
so she can learn.
She's an honor student!
She also has a scholarship!
But she stopped studying at some point.
You did the same thing to me before.
You're pulling me down
because you want to be
the only one at the top!
-That's enough.
-Now I see it.
This conversation isn't about Patricia.
It's about you.
Because until now,
your ego is still bruised.
What do you want me to do?
Just let her sit there all day,
just like what you did before?
Like a worthless nepo husband?
Using the Aragon name as you please?
Thank goodness
she didn't grow up with you!
Because if she did,
she'd end up just like you!
-Boss?
-Pa, that's enough.
What you're doing doesn't seem right.
-Calm down.
-And who are you?
You are not part of our conversation!
Don't get involved!
You aren't talking.
You're causing a scandal.
If you continue this,
we'll sue you for Unjust Vexation,
Grave Threats and Trespassing.
Wait a minute.
There's no need to take it that far.
My family will leave peacefully.
Pa?
You'll go down one day, Diana.
You'll get what's coming to you.
If you can't respect me in my own company,
leave.
Leave my company now!
Get out!
Come with us, Patricia.
You don't need to put up with this hell.
Patricia.
Here's the list of people.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Would you like me
to solve the problem with your husband?
You can't destroy his life.
He did it on his own.
That's not part of your job.
This is my personal life.
Diana…
you are La Familia.
Your personal life
is part of the business.
And part of my job…
is to find out the SWOT.
Strengths, weaknesses,
opportunities,
and most importantly, threats.
I need to know who isn't right for you.
I need to know
who's ruining and hurting you.
Martin can't do anything to hurt me again.
You know I caught him cheating on me
with my best friend.
Carlota, who was my former secretary.
Does Patricia know?
I wouldn't stoop so low
as to destroy her father
just to prove my point to my child.
I won't stoop that low.
I'm nothing like Martin,
who has to tear others down
to prove that I'm right.
If we hadn't gone there,
then we wouldn't have seen her.
Now my day's ruined.
Why did it have to get
to the point of arguing again?
Patricia, the reason I came to your office
is because I'm proud of you.
Because it's your first day at your job.
And who wouldn't get mad at that Diana
when she treats you so badly?
You're the daughter of the owner
yet she mistreats you just like that?
You know what…
Diana just wants to get back at you
because you didn't choose her back then.
Why did you marry him?
Because I thought…
he's the only one who knew…
the real me…
outside of this status,
who would love me completely.
When we were about to marry, I thought,
I would have everything.
The one time…
I disobeyed my Papa…
turned out to cause me
the most harm of all.
As my position in the company
continued to rise higher,
Martin's ego couldn't accept it.
So he never missed any chance…
to make me feel like I wasn't good enough.
That's how much of an idiot I am.
I don't think so.
Maybe naive.
You know, he even turned
my own daughter against me.
Get back to work.
Visit the victims.
Find out if what Patricia
is saying is true.
Yes, ma'am.
But it's not right
to just barge in carelessly!
Wait a minute, Patricia.
Your father is just defending you,
now it's as if he's the bad guy.
Because you don't have to defend me.
I can handle things on my own!
And I'm happy with the job she's given me.
What's important for me
is I have a regular income.
So you are on Diana's side
-over your father's, huh?
-That's not it.
You don't understand
where I'm coming from.
What, now we're too dumb to get you?
-That's not it!
-That's enough!
Before you get mistreated in that company,
you better resign now.
I won't allow Diana to make you suffer
just to get back at me.
You should resign.
Diana, you are meant
-to lead La Familia.
-Papa!
So…
Um, here's the attendance sheet.
It's complete with all
of the employees' signatures.
Well, looks like I'm going to talk to HR
to inform them about your…
summer job here.
Consider this
as your early practicum for the company.
And at the same time,
this will give you an advantage
when you step into college.
I want you to learn…
how to manage a business.
I hope you understand why I'm doing this.
So that I could know
the company's staff better.
And for me to realize the responsibilities
and importance of each one of them.
I hope you don't disappoint me.
I'll do my best.
Good morning, Ms. D, Sir Teddy.
Patricia hasn't come in yet.
Just accept it, Sis.
Kids these days are too sensitive.
Give them a little challenge
and they'll give up right away.
Good morning, Ms. D.
I thought you're never coming back.
I know how to follow through
with my words.
Your payment to me is still not settled.
Once it does I'll leave.
And you'll never see me ever again.
But I can say with my whole heart
that I didn't do anything wrong.
About what my father did…
I already talked to him. I apologize.
No.
Don't apologize for him.
Okay?
Yes?
Do you not have anything to say to me?
I would've already did if there was any.
You're, um…
wearing comfortable shoes today.
-I brought the heels with me.
-Oh.
-I'll wear it in a bit.
-No need.
You're late.
Just finish the things I've told you
to do yesterday.
And then, go to the factory.
I want you to collect all of the reports
from the assembly line
and the logistics there, okay?
I'll change into my heels.
I heard about what happened yesterday.
Uncle Martin is just awful, Dad.
Diana and Patricia can't reconcile.
Because when that happens,
she'll groom Patricia
to become her successor.
And we'll be out of the picture.
Not just in the picture.
We will lose everything.
Take the initiative.
-Get those files now.
-Yes, sir. I'll get them.
-Please, hurry.
-I'll bring them now.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey.
-What?
-Why were you running off
-your mouth yesterday?
-What?
Hey, I had no bad intentions.
I merely just said what I saw.
And Ms. D wants to know everything.
I didn't say anything wrong, okay?
-I had no bad intentions.
-Really?
I don't know what you
talked about with the victims.
You don't know? So you didn't
hear it and made things up?
I didn't make things up.
All I said was that I saw you
with the people from the rally.
That's all!
Okay? I didn't know that Ms. D
would think of it differently.
I helped them out but I ended up
looking like the bad person.
You're just like them, aren't you?
You want me out.
It… It's not like that, Patricia.
-I, uh…
-Sir, here are the files.
Blabbermouth.
-Sir.
-It's all good. Go ahead.
Signed waivers.
The victims Patricia talked to
agreed to the settlement.
You know what, Diana, Patricia is useful.
That kid's excellent.
They didn't just hear
her talk about money.
There's sincerity, empathy.
For the first time,
someone really listened to them.
With this development,
maybe we'd be able
to convince Burger City International
to push through with the partnership.
Did Patricia convince all of them?
There's still a few
who's stubborn about it.
There's a faction of the victims
that didn't sign.
And they're not acting
like ordinary victims.
What do you mean?
It seems like something's inciting them
to reject the settlement.
It seems like they don't just want
a simple compensation.
It's like they want to knock you down.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
-What is it?
-Ms. D, you need to see this.
A new video is circulating.
Do you know one of the most controversial
things to happen at La Familia?
The huge fire incident from then…
that is still unsolved today.
It's possible that Diana Aragon
has something to do with it.
The tragedy at La Familia…
What is this nonsense?
or was it a ploy
to save a failing company?
But based on the official investigation,
there was one person singled out
to be the perpetrator.
Cecilia Pineda.
The question is, why her?
Did they use her to cover up
for the real culprit?
Or did the Aragon family
completely silence her?
According to the record,
Patricia gave out a statement,
who was only eight years old at the time.
She heard that her grandfather
and her mother
were involved in the incident.
Is the saying
that children don't lie, true?
Could this have caused
the rift between the mother and daughter?
Who posted this garbage?
It's just a new account, Ms. D.
Find out where this came from.
And do everything you can
to get rid of it.
Yes, Ms. D.
Let's meet in the training room
in 15 minutes.
I'll teach you everything
you need to do here there.
After the briefing,
I'll give you a tour of the factory.
-Okay.
-I'll get going then.
Have you seen
that trending AI generated video
about the La Familia fire?
I did. It's fake news.
Why did they do it?
For the insurance.
Uh, excuse me!
What AI generated video
of La Familia was it?
-Uh, here.
-…things to happen
at La Familia?
According to the records,
Patricia gave out a statement…
I think…
there's only one person behind this.
Just like how a video
was also created back then
about La Familia's past tragedy.
I did some research.
Patricia's statement back then
barely had any coverage.
You've deleted almost all traces of it.
Because it isn't true.
Which means…
only a few people know of this.
The poisoning…
happened on the same day
as La Familia's anniversary
and the fire.
About the fire incident,
looks like the person behind this
knows a lot about
the inner workings of La Familia.
An inside job?
I want that person to rot in prison.
Diana…
is there something about the fire incident
that could damage
the company's reputation?
Excuse me?
Did you have anything to do with the fire?
How dare you?
What kind of question is that?
My own father died in that incident.
I'm just trying to make sure.
No!
That video spouted nothing but lies!
It was a disgruntled employee
who started the fire.
And it almost led to our collapse.
But whoever is behind this,
they must know something…
that isn't easily known to just anyone.
That's what's scary.
Because they know you.
And whoever they are…
they have a grudge against you.
The huge fire incident from then…
that is still unsolved today.
Mommy! Mommy!
It's possible that Diana Aragon
has something to do with it.
Stop watching that.
But Pa, is it really true?
That the fire was set on purpose
to get the insurance money?
Uh… yes.
It was set on fire by a wacko employee.
They also said that Sis knows something.
-Think it's true?
-Why don't you ask her then?
Hey.
You two,
don't ever ask your sister about this!
-Why not, Pa?
-Just don't.
Let's leave it all in the past.
You called for me?
Patricia.
Tell me the truth.
What truth?
Is this video another one
of your family's schemes?
I don't know anything about it.
This isn't the first time it happened.
First,
it was when I kicked you out of my house.
And now,
it's after your father caused
a scene here.
If we made that video, I won't lie to you.
But would you look at that.
The past has a habit of coming back.
No matter how much you try to bury it.
What do you mean?
When you tried to pin the blame
on me for the fire.
You don't know what you're saying.
Are you going to disregard
my own experiences too?
Just like how you repeatedly made me feel
that what happened was all my fault.
That it was my fault grandfather died.
But now that everything's
rising up to the surface again…
will you tell me the truth?
Was the fire done on purpose
to save the company?
I still remember what you told me
when I was a kid
when the investigators
were interrogating me.
You really believe I'm capable
of doing such a thing?
That I can do such a thing
to my own father?
Is that really how you see me?
All I know…
is that you'll do anything
and sacrifice everything
just for La Familia.
Uh, ma'am,
this is the result
of the investigation of our team.
We also made sure that…
all of the evidence pointing to Patricia
has been erased.
The result of the investigation
by the fire investigators
will reflect that as well.
And by the way,
I've already talked to someone
so that all of this will be blamed
on Cecilia Pineda.
Make sure nothing about this gets out.
Yes, ma'am.
I've already made sure
that everyone's lips are sealed.
I'm sorry, Papa.
I've done everything.
For the sake of everything.
Of the company…
and most of all,
I have to protect Patricia.
What's important is that
you and Patricia are seen together.
You need to show them a united front.
Seems like you don't want me here anyway.
Who told you that I don't want you here?
I can finally do what I've always wanted.
I like it because I worked for it.
I gave it my all,
not just because I'm an Aragon.
Do you think they're planning something?
All I know is
I can't be kicked out of here.
There is someone
who wants to take the company down.
I will never allow anybody
to take down La Familia.
-What was that?
-Help!